trinimotors.com 2015-05-26

# Privacy Policy

**[Contact Us](http://www.trinimotors.com/sendmessage.php) | Sponsors | [Advertising](http://www.trinimotors.com/threads/336-Banner-Advertising-on-TriniMotors-com) | Privacy Policy**

TriniMotors.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: TriniMotors.com.   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us a valid email address. They are used for notifying our members of news/announcements on the site and to assist in utilizing the forum functionality, which may include sharing the information with our trusted partners. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.   
This site contains links to other sites. **TriniMotors** **.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. **Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Data is protected both through physical means and by use of encryption and firewall technology. **Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. **Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Supplementation Information**

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. **Children's Guidelines**

This site prevents children from publicly posting or distributing personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. **Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [admin@trinimotors.com](mailto:admin@trinimotors.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: [Contact Us](http://www.trinimotors.com/sendmessage.php)

**Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  * visit [http://www.trinimotors.com/usercp.php](http://www.trinimotors.com/www.trinimotors.com/usercp.php)

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.trinimotors.com/sendmessage.php).
